// Biology
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following systems protects our body against disease-causing microbes?",
    answer: "Immune system",
    options: [
      "Immune system",
      "Digestive system",
      "Excretory system",
      "Respiratory system"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following immunity is present from our birth?",
    answer: "Innate Immunity",
    options: [
      "Active immunity",
      "Innate Immunity",
      "Passive immunity",
      "Acquired immunity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following food sources has the highest levels of vitamin C?",
    answer: "Black currants",
    options: [
      "Parsley",
      "Broccoli",
      "Orange juice",
      "Black currants"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following vitamin helps in blood clotting?",
    answer: "Vitamin K",
    options: [
      "Vitamin A",
      "Vitamin C",
      "Vitamin K",
      "Vitamin D"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following gas is released out during the process of respiration?",
    answer: "Carbon dioxide",
    options: [
      "Oxygen",
      "Hydrogen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following are the primary causes of water pollution?",
    answer: "Human activities",
    options: [
      "Plants",
      "Animals",
      "Human activities",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following food components is required for the growth and maintenance of the human body?",
    answer: "Both Proteins and Vitamins",
    options: [
      "Proteins",
      "Vitamins",
      "Minerals",
      "Both Proteins and Vitamins"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Egg is a rich source of _______",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Proteins",
      "Vitamins",
      "Minerals",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "____________is the study of the cell, its types, structure, functions and its organelles.",
    answer: "Cell Biology",
    options: [
      "Biology",
      "Cell Biology",
      "Microbiology",
      "Biotechnology"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The tricuspid valve is present between",
    answer: "right auricle and right ventricle",
    options: [
      "Ventricle and pulmonary artery",
      "Ventricle and aorta",
      "left auricle and left ventricle",
      "right auricle and right ventricle"
    ]
  },
];